Sir, the much awaited, much talked, much discussed
listing of ICIC Pru AM AMC is there, Bansal ji and
his friends are also eagerly waiting for
your commentary, sir please tell me
and the listing too, much much much, you said it three times that it will be much much much much better than
you think
and at least when I
recommended this IPO, we said it has a
very strong listing gain and
invest money for the long term, the response was amazing, what do
I say to this response,
good, very good, amazing, excellent,
no, not historic, well
this is historic response and applications worth Rs 3 lakh crore are to
come, it is a big thing for an IPO of Rs 10,000 crore, 600 crore.  This
is a big deal for an IPO of this size.  Number one, number
two, 19 out of the top 20 mutual funds in the country are
in FI, you name it which FI brokerage, there is no
big FI investor
who has not invested money in this company.  This
means that quality of investor quantity is definitely there in
its place.  Everyone
gets a chance to invest Rs 10,600 crore.  This is
why we said that you should
invest in these quality works for both listing gains and long term.  Now let me
tell you that compared to the issue price of ₹2165,
we feel that it will be a very strong
listing.  2625 2675 and
if it gives on listing then it will be on the positive side.
My expectations will be exceeded only,
not exceeded.
Good.
And the reason for this is that if you remember
when the new IPO came, then a day or two
before that we had also done a story about how the
first three-four companies which were listed by ICC Bank,
no doubt then the old
management was there, Bakshi sahab was not there
but they made money and did not give it
in the IPO, this time I want to give credit to
Sandeep Bakshi sahab as well as Nimesh Shah
sahab, both of them did
such pricing after thinking very well, they
want to tell that they take care not
only of the investors of ICICI Mutual Fund but also of the shareholders of the schemes of ICICI Mutual Fund.
So they have
left room for listing.  You can
compare it with HDFC Mul Fund.  They kept the
valuation at least 15 to 20%
lower than HDFC Mutual Fund.  Now a news on top of that,
look at their luck, whatever good he does, good happens to him.
They
maintained a good valuation.  Yesterday the news about your SAB came.  Nothing happened as
feared.
TR, regarding that expense ratio,
people were troubling him repeatedly in the press conference by
asking questions on this
and what will happen if the expense ratio increases,
I had also asked the question to Nimish sir
very nicely, he said nothing will happen,
volume will increase,
growth will come, right,
this is a big thing, so I think
this is going to do wonders, the stock is good for you, you are a
long term investor, I believe that
you should definitely keep it in your portfolio for two-three years, if
you want to protect your portfolio as a short term investor,
keep any stop loss below 247500 for profit.  But what I want to
understand is that sometimes you get good stocks
in allotment and this is
such a story where you do not have to find customers.
Nowadays, people
reach mutual funds by searching for customers themselves.  So whether it is HDFC Mutual
Fund or ICICI Mutual Fund, I
think it is getting ready for a strong listing.
And this compounding
story is at least two-three years old.  We will
see more after that.  I
think there should be no rush to sell it.
Yes, now for new investment, if the
listing naturally happens at 40%, 50% higher level, then it becomes
difficult because the
track record till now has been that the good and
big IPOs, after a strong listing,
then they cool down for two-four quarters, for
two-quarters, for six months,
so now we will not advise you to make a new investment, that
you should buy even at this level, but if
you have got allotment in the old IPO, then
definitely hold it, do not send it in a hurry, all right,
meanwhile come for the pre-opening session.